

#### CONTACT



+974 77 140 825



sarranaili94@hotmail.com



http://linkedin.com/in/sarahnaili-9582b0225



Umm Al Teen St, Doha, Qatar

#### HARD SKILLS

- Adobe Suits
- Microsoft Office
- Pascal
- Autocad 2D
- Technical Drawing
- 3dsmax Revit Architecture
- Adobe Photoshop
- Sketchup
- Planner 5D

# **SOFT SKILLS**

- Color sense
- Attention to details
- Team work
- Time management

#### **HOBBIES**

- Painting
- Sketching
- · Designing DIY furniture
- Reading
- Traveling
- Sport

# NAILI Sarah

# INTERIOR DESIGNER

A multi-skilled, creative and polyvalent interior designer with 2 years of experience; A quick learner who is always open to new ideas; flexible to address challenges and able to effectively perform tasks amid a high-pressure work environment; a seeker of new opportunities with a view to improve my skills and develop my professional career.

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **Interior Design and Decoration**

Tunisie Cuisine | 01/04/2020 - 30/03/2022

#### **Interior Design Internship**

Pro-Tush (Architecture, building, decoration and design specialized firm) | 01/08/2020 - 30/09/2020

## **Installation and Maintenance Internship**

Aziza Othmana Hospital | 04/02/2017 - 22/05/2017 Pharmaghreb (Tunisian pharmaceutical industry) | 13/10/2016 - 05/11/2016 Tunisair (National Airline of Tunisia) | 01/10/2015 - 30/10/2015

## **Production System Piloting Internship**

STEG (Tunisian Electricity and Gaz Company) | 01/03/2016 - 30/03/2016

# **EDUCATION**

#### High Technical Qualification in Interior Design and Decoration

Pilot Academy of Arts and Creation - Tunis, Tunisia | 2018 - 2020

✓ First class honours

# Professional Technician Degree in Automated Production Systems Conduct

Sectorial Training Center in Electricity and Maintenance of Biomedical Equipment - Tunis, Tunisia | 2015 - 2017

#### **Baccalaureate level in Computer Science**

Assad Ibn Furat High School - Oued Ellil Manouba - Tunisia | 2014 - 2015

# **CERTIFICATES**

Autodesk Autocad (Advanced Autocad) Autodesk 3dsMax (Intermediate level)

Pilot Academy of Arts and Creation - Tunis, Tunisia | 2018 - 2020

#### LANGUAGES

- Arabic
- English
- French
- Spanish